Guide to the W. Keith Kennedy papers, 1971-1978.
Kennedy, W. Keith papers, 1971-1978.
- NASULGC, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 34-35)
- Native Americans, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Nematode Lab, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- New Faculty Reception, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- New York Farm Bureau, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- New York Farmers, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- New York State Council of Agricultural Organizations, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- New York State Agricultural Society, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- New York State Association of Refrigerated Warehouses, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- New York State Bankers Association, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- New York State Council of Farmer Cooperatives, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- New York State Department of Law, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- New York State Farm Electrification Council, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 47-48)
- New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- New York State Food Processors, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- New York State Forest Practice Board, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- New York State Grange, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- New York State Horticulture Society, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- New York State Soil and Water Conservation, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Graduate School of Nutrition, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 56-58)
- Correspondence--O, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Ombudsman, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Operation Hitchhike, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- Organic Gardening, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- Ornithology Laboratory, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Overhead, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- Oyer, Edwin B., 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- Correspondence--P, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Pesticides, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 68-69)
- Pesticide Manual, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Pest Management, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Pinchot Institute, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Post-Harvest Physiology, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Presidential Appointments, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Presidential Councilors, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Professional Personnel Other Than Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Professor-At-Large, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Program Funding, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Public Service Commission, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Correspondence--R, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Office of Regional Resources and Development, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Registrar, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Remote Sensing, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- RICOP, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Rome State School Land, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- ROTC, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Rural Development Act, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Rural Development, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Rural Land Use Policy Conference in the Northeast, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Correspondence--S, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Safety Division, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Scholarships, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Schoharie, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Soil Conservation Service, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Soil Conservation Society of America, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Soybean Seminar Proceedings, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Science, Technology, and Society (STS), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Student Credit Hours, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Office of Dean of Students, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Office of Student Records and Finance, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Surplus Equipment, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Correspondence--T, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Transfers, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Transfer Tuition, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Traffic Bureau, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Transportation, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Tropical Agriculture Tour, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Tuition, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Tuition Income Analysis, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Tuition--Children's Scholarship, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Turfgrass, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Television (TV), 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Correspondence--U, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Uihlein Farm, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- University Libraries, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- University of the Philippines, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- University Senate, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- University Senator Luncheons, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Urban Development Research Center, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- U.S. Department of Agriculture.S. Department of Agriculture, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- U.S. Department of Labor.S. Department of Labor, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- U.S. Plant, Soil, and Nutrition Laboratory.S. Plant, Soil, and Nutrition Laboratory, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Correspondence--V, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Van Demark, Noland L., 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 56-58)
- Veterinary College, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Correspondence--W, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Water Resource and Marine Sciences Center, Cornell University, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Wayne County, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Ways and Means, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- Weather Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- Correspondence--XYZ, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Committee on Academic Programs and Policies, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 66)
- Ad Hoc Committee (Jones, Knapp, Peterson, Widom, and Kennedy), 1970 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Administrative Planning Council, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Admissions and Financial Aids Committee, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- Agriculture and the Environment Task Force, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Faculty Salary and Tenure Policies Committee (Plane, R.--Chrm, Schultz, A., Call, D., and Kennedy, K.), 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 71)
- Food Science Advisory Committee, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 72)
- Fruit Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 73)
- Geneva--Study Committee of New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 74)
- Homes and Grounds Committee, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 75)
- Human Affairs Administrative Board, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 76)
- Committee on Independent Courses, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 77)
- International Agriculture Development (IAD) Director Search Committee, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 78-79)
- Jonas Committee (Advisory Council--Committee on Higher Education), 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 80-83)
- Natural Resources Committee (College of Forestry and Cornell University), 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 84-87)
- Natural Resources Subcommittee (Resident Instruction), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 88)
- Board of Natural Resource Organizations, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Microbiology Review Committee, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- New York State Soil and Water Conservation Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 3-5)
- New York State Rural Development Advisory Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
- Nutrition Search Committee, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Pesticide Ad Hoc Committee, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Pesticide Laboratory Committee, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Pesticide Residue Policy Committee, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Poultry Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- College Publications Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 13-15)
- Director of Research Search Committee, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 16-19)
- Rural Development Advisory Council, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Rural Development Seminar Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Soil and Water Management as Related to Water Supplies, Waste Disposal, and Related Areas Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Committee on Status of Blacks at Cornell, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Council of Student Personnel Associates, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Temporary Commission to Study Agricultural Policy, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- University Faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Veterinary Deanship Search Committee, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Ward's Committee, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Water Resources and Marine Sciences Search Committee for Director, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Water Resources, Cornell, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 30-32)
- Water Resources and Marine Sciences Center Review Committee, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 33-35)
- Center of Water Resources, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 36-38)
- SUNY--Water Resources, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Water Resources, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 40-41)
- Water Resources, Cornell, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 42-43)
- Watersheds, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Water Resources and Marine Sciences Governing Board, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 45-46)
- Institute of Environmental Studies (LCC), 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 47-49)
- Environmental Quality Management (LCC), 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
- National Science Foundation (IRRPOS), 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 4-9)
- Water Resources Center, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 10-14)
- Water Resources Governing Board, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 15-17)
- Environmental Agricultural Leaders Forum, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Environmental Center Bills, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- New York State Environmental Conservation Department, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Environmental Plan for New York State, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Environmental Protection Agency, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Environmental Studies Program, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 23-25)
- Center for Environmental Quality Management--General Information, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Environmental Quality Conference with Agriculture, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Center for Environmental Quality Management, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 28-30)
- Center for Environmental Quality Management--Partial Review of the NUS Environmental Feasibility Report, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Faculty Representation for Environmental Studies, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Second Environmental Leaders' Forum, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Center for Environmental Quality Management (CEQM) Governing Board Meeting, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Ad Hoc Faculty Committee for Institute for Environmental Sciences, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Environmental--Civil and Environmental Engineering, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Environmental--Center for Environmental Quality Management, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Environmental--Comparative Environment Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Department of Environmental Conservation, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Environmental--Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Environmental--Directory, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Environmental Education Act, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
- Environmental--Funding, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Environmental--Institute, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Environmental--International Studies and Environment, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Environmental--Land Use and Natural Resource (LUNR), 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
- Environmental--Meetings, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Environmental Meeting, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
- Environmental--"National Environmental Center Bill" and "Muskie-Baker Bill", 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Environmental--National Science Foundation (NSF), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
- Environmental--Organization, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Environmental--C.E. Palm, 1969-1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Environmental--Personnel, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Environmental--Pesticides, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Environmental--Proposed Names, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Environmental Protection Agency, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Environmental--Research Applied to National Needs (RANN), 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 20-21)
- Environmental--Remarks, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Environmental--Science, Technology, and Society (STS), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Environmental--State University, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Environmental--Superhighway, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Environmental--Water Resources Center, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Region II, 1973-1973 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Regional Area II, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- SUNY--Region II, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Regional Meetings--Area II, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 30-32)
- Regional Area II, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 33-35)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Progress Report, Implementation of Master Plan of 1972 (Part I--Narrative), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Progress Report, Implementation of Master Plan of 1972 (Part II--Statistics), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 40-41)
- Official Short Range Enrollment Goals, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Master Plan, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Master Plan, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 44-45)
- Planning Projections, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Master Plan--College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 47-48)
- Master Plan--Cornell University, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 49-50)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
- Campus Academic Plans and Development Plans, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Campus Academic Plan and Development Plans, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Academic Plan for New York State College of Agriculture, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
- Sea Grant Sponsored New York Marina Management Conference, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Sea Grant--Audit Report on Matching Funds For Year One of the New York Sea Grant Program, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Sea Grant--Proposal Submitted for Year IV, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- New York's Sea Grant Program, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Sea Grant, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 11-14)
- Sea Grant, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
- Sea Grant--Proposal for Institutional Sea Grant Support of New York State (Volumes I-III), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 17-19)
- Sea Grant Proposals, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 20-22)
- Sea Grant, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 23-24)
- New York's Sea Grant Program, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Sea Grant, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Agriculture Council, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 27-28)
- Agriculture Council--New York State College of Agriculture, 1959-1968 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Trustee Action--Agriculture Council, 1960-1971 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Agricultural College Council, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Council Management, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 32-34)
- Council Meetings, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 35-36)
- Agricultural College Council, Spring Meeting, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Council Information Sheets, 1961-1971 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Agricultural College Council--Member Lists, 1957-1971 (Box 19, Folder 39-41)
- Agricultural College Council--Proposed Members, 1962-1971 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
- Council--Meeting, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
- Council, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5-7)
- Council Meeting, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 8-10)
- Agricultural College Council, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
- Agricultural College Council Meeting, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
- Agricultural College Council, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 15-16)
- Agricultural College Council Meeting, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- College Council Meeting, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 18-19)
- Agricultural College Council Meeting, Spring, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Agricultural College Council Meetings, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 21-22)
- Agricultural College Council Meeting, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 23-24)
- College Council Meeting, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Agricultural College Council--Spring Meeting, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Council For New York State College of Agriculture Meeting, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Agricultural College--Advisory Council Meeting (Geneva), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 28-30)
- Circular Letters and Directives, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- New York State College of Agriculture and Experiment Stations Council Reports to Board of Trustees, 1959-1971 (Box 21, Folder 2-6)
- Biological Sciences--Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Budgets, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Budgets--Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Budget--Biological Sciences, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Budget--Course Load, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Budget--Cornell University, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Budget--Department of Education, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Budget--Faculty, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Budget--Geneva, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Budget--General, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Budget--Human Ecology, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Budget--Industrial and Labor Relations, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Budgets--Statutory Colleges, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 19-20)
- Budget--Veterinary College, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Budget--Biological Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Budgets (Dworsky and Lynn), 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Budget Situation, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Budget--Extension, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Budget--Geneva, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Supplemental Budget Request, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 27-28)
- Budget--Water Resources and Marine Sciences Center, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Budget--Veterinary College, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Tompkins County Area Development, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 31-32)
- Teaching Assistants, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 33-35)
- SUNY--Biological Sciences, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Graduate School of Nutrition, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 37-38)
- Bankhead Jones Teaching Funds, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- College of Agriculture, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 40-42)
- Salary Adjustments, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 43-45)
- Audit and Control, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 46-47)
- Audit and Control--Agriculture, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 48-49)
- Audit and Control--Biological Sciences, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- Audit and Control--Human Ecology, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 51)
- Audit and Control--Industrial and Labor Relations, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 52)
- Audit and Control--Nutrition, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 53)
- Audit and Control--Veterinary College, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 54)
- Trustee Action, 1960-1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Policies and Procedures For Promotions in Rank, Vice President For Academic Affairs--Brown, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Policies and Procedures, 1960-1968 (Box 22, Folder 3-5)
- Policies and Procedures, 1969-1972 (Box 22, Folder 6-8)
- Deans and Directors (D&D) Meeting Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 9-12)
- D&D Meeting Minutes, 1966-1969 (Box 22, Folder 13-15)
- College of Agriculture--Endowed Accounting, 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 16-18)
- Tuition and Fee Information, 1968-1972 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- College Regulations (Malone, V.), 1947-1972 (Box 22, Folder 20-21)
- Policies, 1931-1958 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Academic Plan, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 23-25)
- Comments on the Academic Plan, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 26-28)
- President's Study Committee--Pertinent Material, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 29-31)
- President's Study Committee, College of Agriculture--Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
- President's Study Committee--Name Change, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- President's Study Committee--Notices, Agenda, and Memos, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- President's Study Committee--Questions to Agriculture Faculty, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- President's Study Committee--Report on Student-Faculty Relationships, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- President's Study Committee--Resident Instruction, 1962-1967 (Box 23, Folder 10-13)
- President's Study Subcommittee--Applied and Basic Research (Pimentel--Chrm., Levine, Plaisted, Plane), 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- President's Study Subcommittee--Extension and Public Service (Risley--Chrm., Curtis, Harrington, Shallengerger), 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- President's Study Committee--Summary of Comments Received From Faculty of Agriculture, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- President's Study Subcommittee--Professional Education (Cuykendall--Chrm., Foote, Layne, Warren), 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- President's Study Committee--Kennedy's Notes, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- President's Study Committee--College of Agriculture, 1964-1966 (Box 23, Folder 19-20)
- Bailey, L. H., 1909 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Report of President's Committee on Biological Sciences, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- President's Study Committee (Bruckner, Dr. J. H.), 1957-1964 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- President's Committee Report--Comments From Faculty College of Agriculture, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder 24-28)
- President's Study Committee--Comments From Outside of College, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- President's Study Committee--Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder 30-31)
- President's Study Committee--Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- President's Study Committee--External Consultants, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- President's Study Committee--Cooperative Extension, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- President's Study Committee--Geneva (New York State Agriculture Experiment Station Report), 1966 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- President's Study Committee--Graduate School, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- President's Study Committee--College of Home Economics, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- President's Study Committee--Mission and Goals of the College (The Need for Long-Range Planning), 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- President's Study Committee--International Agricultural Development, 1961-1965 (Box 23, Folder 39-49)
- Assistant to the President (Barlow, J. R.), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Board of Trustees, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Counsel, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Dean of the Faculty, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- President, 1974-1974 (Box 23, Folder 45-46)
- Provost, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 47-48)
- State Relations Coordinator, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Treasurer, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
- Vice President for Administration, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Vice President for Campus Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Vice President for Planning, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Vice President for Research, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Vice Provost (Barlow, Mark), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Vice Provost (McKeegan, Paul), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Vice Provost (Risley, R. F.), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Committee of Chairmen, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Deans and Directors (D&D) Agendas, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- D&D Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Deans' Council, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Department Heads' Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Provost--Statutory Deans' Meetings, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Statutory Deans' Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Meetings With Department Chairman and Faculty, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Associate Chancellor for Special Projects, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 20-22)
- SUNY--Budget 1976, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- SUNY--Director of Budget (Anslow), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- SUNY--Campus Development, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- SUNY--Campus Liaison (Block, M.), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- SUNY--Chancellor, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- SUNY--Conference of Presidents, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- SUNY--Construction Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 30-33)
- SUNY--Counsel, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- SUNY--Course Audits by Older Adults, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- SUNY--Executive Vice Chancellor, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- SUNY--Faculty Grants, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- SUNY--Faculty Senate, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- SUNY--Faculty Senate Minutes, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- SUNY--Finance and Business, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- SUNY--Institute for Public Policy Alternatives, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- SUNY--Institutional Research, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- SUNY--Legislative Relations (Freedman, Irving H.), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- SUNY--Newsletter, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- SUNY--New York City Office, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- SUNY--Policy and Planning, Associate Chancellor Ingler, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 47)